<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pinwheel</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pinwheel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 17:06:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jamf Rolling Updates</title>
      <link>/blog/jamf-rolling-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 17:06:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/jamf-rolling-updates/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viewing Configuration Profiles in Terminal</title>
      <link>/blog/viewing-configuration-profiles-in-terminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 13:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/viewing-configuration-profiles-in-terminal/</guid>
      <description>Often times I find myself wanting to view a print out of currently installed configuration profiles on a machine, but either can&amp;rsquo;t or don&amp;rsquo;t want to use the GUI. This would normally consist of going to System Preferences &amp;gt; Profiles to view a list of all profiles installed.
This method is useless if I am ssh&amp;rsquo;d into a box or am running a script remotely, etc.
You can run profiles -C in terminal to get a basic output of your profiles but if they were created using Jamf, then they&amp;rsquo;re not named in a very human-readable format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Pinwheel with Hugo and Firebase</title>
      <link>/blog/building-pinwheel-with-hugo-and-firebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 15:04:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/building-pinwheel-with-hugo-and-firebase/</guid>
      <description>The website you are reading right now was brought to you with the help of Hugo and Firebase. This combination of tools has allowed me to spin up a live website faster than I ever have before; &amp;lt; 1 hour to a live skeleton site. The free tier of Firebase made it really quick and easy to just pick up and get going, and since it is made by Google, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even need to create a second account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 11:24:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Kyle LeBlanc - Pinwheel is a (mostly) technical blog dedicated to topics of systems administration/enterprise management in the context of macOS. Frequent topics include installers and packaging, automation tooling, software and OS deployment, MDM, Apple’s command line tools, bash, and Jamf.
The words and views on this blog are my own and do not represent my employer.
Current: Liberty Mutual
Previous: PatientPing, Wayfair, Hill Holliday, MIT Lincoln Labs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating New Web Dev Environments</title>
      <link>/blog/automating-new-web-dev-environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 13:52:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/automating-new-web-dev-environments/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We need to re-image your laptop&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Time to nuke and repave&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Your machine is totally borked&amp;rdquo;
No one wants to hear those words come from IT. Especially developers. I&amp;rsquo;ve had to deliver this news more times than I can count from users destroying their own machines either from messing with permissions, malware, or just from updates gone wrong.
I&amp;rsquo;ve done my best to help alleviate some of this pain from the dev crowd by assisting in automating their environment setup on a net-new machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Active Directory Domain Migration on MacOS</title>
      <link>/blog/active-directory-domain-migration-on-macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 11:28:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/active-directory-domain-migration-on-macos/</guid>
      <description>Joining Windows machines to an AD domain is easy, intuitive, and downright simple. The same can&amp;rsquo;t really be said for machines running macOS. The task of binding these devices to the same AD world that your Windows machines are on can be tricky and cumbersome, but this is becoming all the more common as macOS is taking up a larger seat in the enterprise/corporate world.
So we know how finicky binding macOS to AD is, now imagine automating the process to swap from one AD to a new one, on almost 1,400 macOS machines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>